Finding Aid for the Abraham Polonsky papers, 1946-1999 (bulk 1970s-1990s) LSC.2233
UCLA Library Special Collections
- The Rosenbergs: Collected Visions of Artists and Writers edited by Rob A. Okun - book, c. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Inscribed by [Okun?].
- Thomas Mann the Story of a Novel: The Genesis of Doctor Faustus - book, c. 1961 (Box 19)
  Handwriting on dust jacket.
- To Illuminate our Time: The Blacklisted Teleplays of Abraham Polonsky - soft cover book, c. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Troubled Mandarins (The) by Timon in Masses and Mainstream, 1956 Aug (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Truth about Tubby and Slim (The) by Stan Polonsky - book, c. 1993 (Box 19)
- Typed manuscript pages about Polonsky, no date (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Possible book by unknown author.
- Typed manuscript pages that appears to for a book about about Polonsky, no date (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Typescript manuscript of annotated script pages (no title), no date (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Typescript pages (no title), no date (Box 13, Folder 1)
  May be preliminary pages of Paul Buhle's biography on Polonsky.
- UCLA Screenwriting Showcase Lifetime Achievement Award plaque, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Visit from St. Nicholas (A) by Clement C. Moore, c. 1849 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Small booklet-like publication.
- Wassaja - screenplay by Polonsky, no date (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Watercolor painting (not signed), no date (Box 20, Folder 1)
- WGA letter withdrawing writer's credit from Fear No Evil, 1990 Aug 22 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- What Makes Hollywood Run Now? By Budd Schulberg from The New York Times magazine (photocopy), 1960 Apr 27 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- What's Wrong; Walls - videotape recording, no date (Box 16)
- Willie Boy - certificate of recognition (in foreign language, possibly Czech), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Willie Boy - final screenplay by Abraham Polonsky, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Willie Boy - final screenplay by Polonsky (2 copies), no date (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Willie Boy - Variety film review, 1969 Oct 22 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- World Above (The) - introduction manuscript, 1998 Apr (Box 13, Folder 9)
  With note for Paul Buhle
- World Above (The) (reissue) - book cover sample, no date (Box 15, Folder 1)
- World of Brotherhood and Guilt: Polonsky as Author (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Notes on unfinished novel.
- Writers at Work: The Paris Review Interviews - book, c. 1958 (Box 18)
  Removed note from Jean Stein to Box 14, Folder
- You Are There - list of writers and titles, no date (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Zenia's Way book review, 1980 Mar 28 (Box 13, Folder 8)